

SAMUEL ODINAKA EZEH

I am a full stack developer

- ✓ samuelblessed38@gmail.com
- **J** 09034605582
- 🛪 3rd Avenue I close Festac Town., 102101 Festac
- ನ್ Male
- Nigerian
- cool-moxie-9c7571.netlify.app
- in linkedin.com/in/samuel-ezeh-62797018a

SKILLS

Javascript

React

Redux

Nodejs

Python

Html

Css

Bootstrap

Mongodb

Firebase

HOBBIES

- Coding
- Solving maths problems

EDUCATION

Bsc Physics

Apr 2014 - Aug 2018

Benue State University, Makurdi

A graduate of physics from Benue State University, Makurdi.

EMPLOYMENT

Frontend developer internship

Mar 2020 - Mar 2021

MountainBlue, Lagos

As a frontend developer, I developed user interfaces using react and other tools for better users experience.

Frontend developer

Apr 2021 - Present

Optimus pro, Lagos

I am responsible for developing user interfaces, writing logical functions and implementation of functionalities for better experiences using redux, react, mui, etc

PROFILE

I am a frontend react developer with great knowledge of design architecture. I have 2 years of active experience in web development. My vast knowledge of mui, css, reactjs, redux, etc, are key for better placement. I have strong affinity to learning new technologies while becoming better developer.

CERTIFICATES

Google certified digital marketer I am a certified digital marketer

Sep 2019